dowtimesfinance.com 2016-10-25

# Privacy Policy - Dow Times Finance

## PRIVACY Statement and Info

dowtimesfinance is the owner and operator of the property located at http://dowtimesfinance.com (the “Website” or the “Site”), has created this Privacy+Security Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of your personal information. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Customer Assistance by sending an email to contact@dowtimesfinance.com.

## Consent

dowtimesfinance only collects, uses, and/or discloses your personally identifiable information with your consent. This privacy policy identifies the ways in which your personally identifiable information will be collected, used, and disclosed. In addition, the Site will ask for your express consent in connection with various offers and events. Regardless, by using the Site and/or by providing DTF with your personally identifiable information and engaging in a transaction with dowtimesfinance you thereby consent to dowtimesfinance collection, use, and disclosure as described herein.

## Personally Identifiable Information Collected by dowtimesfinance

    * In connection with your use of our Site, we may collect and store the following information:
    * The domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Site;
    * The e-mail addresses of users who communicate with us via the Site or via e-mail;
    * Aggregate information on what pages on our Site users access or visit;
    * Information provided by the user, such as through registration on the Site, e-mail update requests and general requests for
    * information (This may include information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information);
    * Information identifying you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number; and

## How dowtimesfinance Uses Your Personal Information

In General: By providing dowtimesfinance with your personally identifiable information in connection with your use of dowtimesfinance services and/or any of the features/functions of the Site, you consent to dowtimesfinance.com collection and use of your Personally Identifiable Information as follows:

      * To provide the products and services requested via the Site;
      * To provide customer support (including the administration of Site usage, monitoring traffic levels, and contacting you regarding improvements we make to our Site and services);
      * To manage your account;
      * To analyze your use of the products and services offered by dowtimesfinance (including the use of your IP address to analyze trends, administer the Sties, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use);
      * To improve upon the products and services offered by dowtimesfinance
      * To provide targeted marketing to you of products and services offered by dowtimesfinance and/or third parties associated with dowtimesfinance
      * To enforce dowtimesfinance terms and conditions (including the terms and conditions of this privacy policy); and
      * To otherwise conduct dowtimesfinance business as otherwise described to you.

We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

Cookies: A cookie is a small data file that certain webSite write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the Site uses to track the pages you’ve visited. When you register at the Site, dowtimesfinance uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We may use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track information while you are on our Site. Cookies also enable you to enter the Site as a registered user without having to log on each time. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser.You do not need to have cookies turned on to use the Site. However, if you turn off cookies, then you may not be able to utilize certain features of the Site.

## Disclosure to Third Parties:

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone, except with your consent and as permitted by law, in the following situations:

Limited Information to Providers / Business Partners: dowtimesfinance may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties, though such summary information will not identify any specifics related to you. We partner with certain third parties to provide specific services. For example, internet connectivity, computer crime investigation, incident response, web hosting, etc. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except in conjunction with providing these services.

Business Transactions: In the event dowtimesfinance goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

## Choices/Opt Out

If you prefer that we not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures; that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law).If you receive communications from us that you do not want to receive, you can opt-out from receiving these communications, by specifically telling us to stop sending them to you. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email or emailing us.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

We will apply the Opt-Out policies discussed above in the event we propose to disclose your information to a third party.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect data when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
